Yeah
Let's ride
Sunrise paints the heartland gold,
Another day to break the mold
Got my rig, a trusty friend
On this road that'll never end
Beneath the wide and starry sky
Embracing this freedom's cry
From the mountains to the plains
Watching where the city stands
Yeah, we're singing 'bout freedom, trucks, and guns
Oh, underneath that blazing sun
A good old burger made in the USA
Living out our dreams the American way
Got that bass thumping with a little bit of twang
Letting that Liberty Bell ring and hang
Two-lane blacktop, windows down, cruising through a dusty town
A little bit of hip-hop beat shuffling to my own two feet
This ain't just a way of life, it's cutting through the noise and strife
With a rifle in the rack, ain't no turning back
Here we're singing 'bout freedom, trucks, and guns
Oh, underneath that blazing sun
A good old burger made in the USA
Living out our dreams the American way
Got that bass thumping with a little bit of twang
Letting that Liberty Bell ring and hang
From the fields of Idaho to the Texas heat
Grilled onions on a sizzling patty, can't be beat
This is the sound of America, raw and true
For the red, white, and blue, me and you
Made in the USA